nexus404.com 2013-04-03

# Disclaimer & Privacy Policy | TFTS Technology, Gadgets & Curiosities

## [Disclaimer & Privacy Policy](http://nexus404.com/tfts-disclaimer/ "Permanent Link to Disclaimer & Privacy Policy")

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at TFTS. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. Our privacy policy is in plain English and will only take a few moments to read and understand.  
**  
Site Tracking**

We have a simple web statistics program running – Sitemeter – that tracks how many times each page is visited. When you visit a page, information is logged that contains your domain name (aol.com, for example), date, time, and pages visited. There is no personally identifiable information. The information we collect is:

  * Used to improve the content on our site
  * Never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes

**Email Addresses**

We log your email address in two situations:

  * TFTS Newsletter – We keep track of email addresses when people sign up for our newsletter. The email address you enter for the newsletter will never be sold or transferred to any other organization. You have the ability to unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time. The form for subscribing and unsubscribing to the newsletter are available on this site and are included in every email that is sent out.
  * Post comments – We keep track of email addresses when people uses this feature. We do this to make sure that someone doesn’t abuse the feature. TFTS will never divulge your name & email to anyone.

If for any reason you receive an email from us and you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending e-mail to tfts@nexus404.com.

**Cookies**

Cookies are a method of tracking information you enter on a web site using a file on your computer. We do use a cookie to log whether you’ve visited the site before. No personal information is written to the cookie at all. It is primarily used to save you time by automatically populating forms in our discussion forum, and other locations on the site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on TFTS send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

TFTS has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Links**

This site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other site.  
**  
How You Can Contact Us**

We can be reached via our contact e-mail to tfts@nexus404.com.

**Disclaimer**

Though TFTS tries its utmost to present accurate, up to date information (invariably based on official press releases), TFTS makes no representations as to accuracy, completeness, currentness, suitability, or validity and this site will not be liable, or be held accountable, for any errors, omissions, or delays in this information or any losses, injuries, or damages arising from its display or use.

_All information is provided on an as-is basis for entertainment purposes only._

If in doubt please refer to a product’s official website (we do our best to offer valid links to official product sites where possible) for current product information prior to making an informed consumer choice.
